virtualemployee.com 2013-03-26

# Privacy Statement -

## VirtualEmployee.com Privacy Statement

The following statement delineates the confidentiality regulations and privacy practices for VirtualEmployee website. This privacy statement is applicable to all linked pages and related documents of VirtualEmployee website. This privacy policy is amendable. VirtualEmployee holds the right to add clause(s) or to delete clause(s). It may also revise the existing clauses. Changes after amendment(s), if any, would be duly incorporated in this privacy document.

#### **1\. VirtualEmployee’s Privacy Policy**

VirtualEmployee values the personal information of its users, and cares about the privacy and confidentiality of user information. VirtualEmployee makes sure that all forms of user information amassed, when users are using its website, are regulated as per norms.

#### **2\. Purview of the Policy**

The privacy policy is meant for those internet users who use VirtualEmployee’s website and services, and while doing so dispense with their personal and organizational information. This privacy policy is irrelevant for those users, who do not share a business relationship or a service relationship with VirtualEmployee, or do not use VirtualEmployee’s website or its associated services. VirtualEmployee website may be linked to other sites, including social networking sites, which have their own privacy rules. VirtualEmployee will not be liable for any breach or defiance of the privacy practices or confidentiality policies of the linked sites.

#### **3\. How personal information is collected?**

VirtualEmployee collects personal information of its users. When a user visits the “Getting started” section of VirtualEmployee website and register himself/herself, VirtualEmployee asks for his/her name, e-mail id, company name, company website, contact no, country and state of residence, the specific VirtualEmployee service that he/she is interested in, time zone, job specification or details of the work he/she is looking to outsource, and the skill set that the employee should have. VirtualEmployee also seeks for user’s name, e-mail id, and his/her comments while he/she fills out the feedback form. These apart, VirtualEmployee may, from its own server, obtain and document user information such as the IP address, cookies, and the page the user requested.

#### **4\. Usage and Sharing of Information**

VirtualEmployee ensures that all forms of personal information collected from users are protected and shared in accordance with the laid out provisions of the privacy statement. All forms of user information that are collected by VirtualEmployee are not shared with any third party website, service partners, or VirtualEmployee’s employees. VirtualEmployee may share user information:

    * If the user is willing to share his/her information for business, promotional, or other purposes.
    * While VirtualEmployee finds an employee for an employer.
    * While VirtualEmployee finds the requested service for the user.
    * With service partners, with prior approval from the user.
    * While VirtualEmployee responds to any summons from courts, regulatory authorities, or government agencies.
    * If the user, while using VirtualEmployee’s website or the services provided by VirtualEmployee, infringes on user terms and agreements.

Users may also ask VirtualEmployee to delete or dispose of their personal information from VirtualEmployee’s database and records. To delete or dispose of posted information, users need to send a request e-mail to [**sales@virtualemployee.com**](mailto:sales@virtualemployee.com)

#### **5\. Cookies**

Cookies may be sent to users’ computers while users navigate through VirtualEmployee website. These cookies are meant to retrieve information when users revisit VirtualEmployee website. These cookies will not harm the user’s system, or thwart his/her privacy arrangements.

#### **6\. Queries and comments**

In case of any general information on privacy-related issues, queries, complaints, [**info@virtualemployee.com**](mailto:info@virtualemployee.com) or supposed infringements of privacy, users can e-mail at or [**sales@virtualemployee.com**](mailto:sales@virtualemployee.com) or can call at 1-(760) 284 4609 (USA), (+44) 020 8099 3086 (U.K.), or (+91) 120 468 0000 (India). Users can also contact through fax no: 1-(760) 284 6966 (USA). Users can provide their feedback, feedforward, suggestions, and comments by filling out the VirtualEmployee’s feedback form.
